

Contact

- Cairo, Egypt
- **** +20 112 4269 532
- ahmed.m.moneem@gmail.com
- Attps://ahmedmohamed26.github.io/
- https://github.com/ahmedmohamed2 6
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/iahmedm ohamed/
- **f** https://www.facebook.com/iAhmmed Mohamed
- https://www.instagram.com/ahmed.m. moneem/

Ahmed Mohamed AbdEl Moneim

FRONT END DEVELOPER

About

Hi, i'am Ahmed Mohamed an energetic and enthusiastic frontend web developer eager to learn new technologies and build amazing stuff.I'm 26 years old ,up I am enjoying building elegant and professional web pages in a modern way. I have developed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Reactjs , Nodejs and other skills to help me fulfill high qualifications and Finished Military Service in Mar 2017.

Experience

Front end developer Proemcs | May 2019 - Present

- Create projects with angular +6 or Reactis or ionic 4
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD | | ProtoType To Pug|S & SCSS

Front end developer Valux Apps | Jan 2018 - April 2019

- Create projects with angular +6
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

Skills

Angula	ar +6
--------------------------	-------

Rxjs

Node Js (basics)

Typescript

Javascript

Json

• scss

Bootstrap 4

CSS3

• XD

ReactJS

Redux (basics)

• Ionic 4

• ES6

• oop js

GulpJS

• Git

Pug|S

HTML5

Jquery

Education

2011 - 2015

Cairo Higher institutes

i'm a graduted system and information with Bachelor degree, Mokattam I've Learning In Cairo Higher institutes HTML, FrontPage, Economic, Marketing, Feasibility Study, Information Security, Network Security